const STORE = [
    {
        question: "What ranking did UCLA receive amongst public universities within the United States?",
        answer: ["13th place", "1st place", "5th place", "3rd place"],
        correctAnswer: "1st place"
    },
    {
        question: "What are the school colors?",
        answer: ["Red and Gold", "Blue and Hazel", "Blue and Gold", "White and Blue"],
        correctAnswer: "Blue and Gold"
    },
    {
        question: "What is said to happen if you touch the water in the inverted fountain more than once before graduation?",
        answer: ["You stay an extra quarter for each additonal touch", "You receive that many A's that quarter", "You stay an extra year for each additional touch", "Nothing"],
        correctAnswer: "You stay an extra quarter for each additonal touch"
    },
    {
        question: "Which dining hall is the latest addition to UCLA?",
        answer: ["Covel", "Cafe 1919", "Feast", "Bruin Plate"],
        correctAnswer: "Bruin Plate"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the school mascot?",
        answer: ["Joe Bruin", "Traveler", "Anteater", "Grizzly Bear"],
        correctAnswer: "Joe Bruin"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the signature hand clap amongst UCLA students called?",
        answer: ["3 clap", "8 clap", "Bruin Clap", "What clap?"],
        correctAnswer: "8 clap"
    },
    {
        question: "How big is the UCLA campus compared to other UC campuses?",
        answer: ["Smallest", "Second largest", "Second smallest", "Third largest"],
        correctAnswer: "Second smallest"
    },
    {
        question: "Which desserts shop is well known amongst students in Westwood?",
        answer: ["Diddy Riese", "Snow Monster", "Blockheads", "Baskin Robins"],
        correctAnswer: "Diddy Riese"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following were the four original buildings in UCLA?",
        answer: ["Royce Hall, Haines Hall, Powell Library, Humanities Building", "Royce Hall, Boelter Hall, Young Hall, Humanities Building", "Powell Library, Boelter Hall, Physics Building, Franz Hall", "Kerckhoff Hall, La Kretz Hall, Law Building, Moore Hall"],
        correctAnswer: "Royce Hall, Haines Hall, Powell Library, Humanities Building"
    },
    {
        question: "How did the rivalry between UCS and UCLA begin?",
        answer: ["USC students stole a 295 lb bell from UCLA", "USC students unleashed 20,000 crickets onto UCLA's campus", "UCLA students broke Tommy's sword", "UCLA students dropped manure onto the USC campus"],
        correctAnswer: "USC students stole a 295 lb bell from UCLA"
    }
  ];